INGABIRE Marie Immaculée

Kigali-Rwanda

Phone: +250-786-024-528
Email: imimaculee@gmail.com

Profile: A young visionary Software Engineer experienced in all facets of manufacturing and engineering environments. Strong work ethic with problem-solving skills with meticulous attention to detail. Excellent communication skills in conjunction with excelling in performance results either individually or within a team environment.

EDUCATION

• SheCanCode graduate :coding program

May 2022- Dec2022

• University of Rwanda; College of Science and Technology

2011-2015

Bachelors of Electronics and Telecommunications Engineering degree

• Lycée Notre Dame De Cîteaux

Advanced Level: Mathematics -Physics and Chemistry

2007-2010

• Ordinary Level

2004-2007

WORK EXPERIENCE AND INTERNSHIPS

• Rwanda Youth in Agribusiness Forum/Minagri: Intern

2022-2023

Data Collection and Data Entry for Market food prices

• Global Professional Services in Eswatini :

March -Dec 2020

Role: Software Developer Intern

Description:

- Provided beneficial technical support and customer service to clients researched and analyzed client' issues, and maintained various PC hardware and software.
- Installed operating systems, configured servers, and worked on the development and implementation of new processes and procedures to increase the quality and efficiency of customer service as much as possible
- Coordinated new employees and pro-actively participated in weekly team meetings with managers and the Board of Directors.
- Maintained documents and records, executed various clerical duties, and performed other tasks as required.
- Identified problems and suggested solutions to the customers.

Delivering technical support over the phone, email, or in-person to the customer

- TRES (Trust Engineering Solution)Ltd, Telecom company
 Intern

 Sept2015-May2017
 - Testing, troubleshooting and correcting Antenna and RF Line
 - Perform and analyze drive testing; walk test in Network Optimization
 - Auditing training on Quality Management Systems: QMS ISO 9001:2015
 - RBS configuration, Mini-link Transmission, routing and switching
- Equity Bank: Relationship Officer Operation May 2017- June 2019
 Customer call center and data support Entry with MS excel and power point

VOLUNTEERING AND ACCOMPLISHMENT

- Certificate and Volunteerism at Power-Africa IEEE Conference 2022(IEEE: Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers): Customer care support
- Volunteering at Rwanda Youth in Agribusiness Forum /MINAGRI: Monitoring market prices for various commodities as settled in the system of e-Soko.
- Certificate of Toastmasters International Public speaking club
- Certificate of Akazi Kanoze Youth empowerment
- Women in innovation Program Certificate

SKILLS

- Customer Support services
- Microsoft excel, Microsoft word, Microsoft Power Point, Outlook
- Computer skills and coding: Html, CSS, JavaScript ,React ,NodeJs, Mongo DB, UI-UX Design
- Communication skills
- Leadership skills
- Time management skills, soft skills ,self-awareness skills

LANGUAGES USED

• English ,French and Kinyarwanda :Fluently and Intermediate both speaking and writing

I hereby certify that the information given above is true to my knowledge